[{"answer": "I'm just fine, Piers.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'm just absolutely thrilled that we've got the president talking about solutions and also I'm very grateful that we've got a bipartisan effort in the Senate to try to address the issue that America, the United States has been facing.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "What is your verdict on what he announced today?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'm not going to plea to any charge.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "How do you plead to that charge?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it is terrible, unimaginable tragedy has taken place in the United States in regards to people, I believe, that have mental health issues that have created terrible tragedy.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "What is your position on where we are with the gun control debate, and what do you think may actually be done to try and deal with America's burgeoning gun violence?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Piers, I didn't see that interview.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "How did you feel on a human level about that moment?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Do you genuinely not believe that America's gun crime rate would fall if you removed guns from circulation rather than increased the volume of guns in circulation?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, I want to make it very clear.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "As an American, what do you feel about the fact that they believe that right supersedes anything else including, you know the rights of your son to not be murdered by that weapon, if you take it to its logical conclusion?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Well, they're much less successful than they used to be, and that's the point that I'm trying to make to my colleagues.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "In reality, how successful are the NRA at doing that?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "I most certainly do.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Do you think that people's views would change if they, too, had to go through what you've been through?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Well, a number of factors led to this.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Why did you do it?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Well, first, let me make it very, very clear that the sheriff is not the law enforcement officer that has jurisdiction over the Milwaukee Police Department.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I object to the Hollywood voice.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "How on Earth does that kind of rhetoric to the American people serve any kind of sensible, rational purpose?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "I don't have those statistics.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "In your time as the sheriff, how many people in Milwaukee, to your certain knowledge, have defended themselves and their family at home by firing a firearm?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "ORGAN: I'm not sure how honest it can be if you haven't got a clue about any of the statistics involving people defending themselves with firearms at home in Milwaukee.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Or are you just going to continue to talk over me?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "ARRETT: Let me make a couple of quick points.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "What is your reaction to what the sheriff was just saying?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "I didn't interrupt you, mayor.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Sheriff, do you support the background check?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "What I support is a prosecutor's office and a judiciary that hammers the people who illegally use a firearm in the commission of a crime.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Yes or no, do you support the idea of background checks for all gun trades?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "-- start by enforcing the laws that are on the books first before we start penalizing law abiding citizens.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Can you answer the question?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "From what I've been hearing from referees that are on the field -- and everybody is off the record because they don't want to -- they fear retribution.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "I mean, what is the nature of the specific allegation?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "There's always a way of getting better.", "docId": "130129pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "Is there a better way of doing the grading system, a more transparent way, perhaps, so that you can avoid this kind of innuendo and smearing?", "qSentId": 513}]